All right, we'll start using the trouble.
We're going to go into the trouble.
Two ladies.
Three of them.
We're going to have the occasion by the pastor of Apocentrum.
Assembly Church, Mr. Fisher.
Thank you.
Thank you, Mr. Fisher.
If you were, just value it.
With me, Father, we thank you today for this gathering.
And that we asked him to invite you into this meeting to give us our leaders, wisdom and knowledge
and just allow them to do the business of the community as a bit of this
to citizens.
I'm also special pre-order for the police and the fire and first responders
and all the civil servants that serve in this great community and even, you know,
the citizens, less of these people that lead, guide and drag, so that we can have a nice
safe and wonderful place to not only live, but to raise our children, grandchildren, and
less are community and Jesus name.
Thank you.
Please join me in the fight.
I would like to introduce you to the fire of the United States of America,
to introduce you to another for which it stands.
One nation under God in the Gospel, with a liberty and justice for all.
Thank you.
I have two words on the public input, and I'm scheduled personal appearances, and I want to
to address the authority on any of the agenda items.
There being none out of five of us can send agenda staff are asking that item six and seven
be placed on the agenda item.
The wording here says eight, but that's on the state.
We're in an item eight, and also just item six and seven for the consent agenda.
We have a motion to approve.
And a second please.
Second.
Go home.
Johnson.
Western.
All right.
So?
God.
I can.
For.
All right.
If you activate is approved management, the GreenBook.
4.
Number 17 slash 18 dash 4, the ultimate Susan for phase 1 of engineering.
Of streets of New Jersey from West Central Avenue, Main Street to Be Streep.
North West.
Tyler, and Alicia.
And Sean.
So this is for the engineering industry of the Street and the water line.
and the water lines, and there's a little bit of sewer lines on central from Maine to
D Street Northwest.
And it also includes the water lines that they're there, that we have had a recent
complaint from DQ on A Street, that they're trucking in about recently, and I mean, this
will hopefully take care of that.
They've had rusty water and kind of low flowing levels still isn't limits by low for us.
And so this will hopefully, once we reach this in the air, we can go in there and put this
in water line in.
So this is basically from Maine to the truck route.
That's the other way.
I don't know.
This is West Central.
Yeah.
And the important thing about this project is getting this project taken care of,
then we can start working on the condition of the street.
We've always held off on the street because of the poor condition of the utilities.
And which side of the street and the line is going to be on?
We'll talk about putting it on the,
we'll talk about putting the water line on the north side because the power pole set on the south side.
We're going to try to move the water line out of the street if possible and put it underneath the sidewalk.
Protects it there. You're not going to have a phone company or somebody plow them through the water line that's under a sidewalk if it's up there.
So at the end of the day, we have a leak on it too, they're not digging up the street or a fence.
You got to pay on it.
What's the treatment facility that's there on this side of the street?
You can see that there really is very close to the sidewalk.
That's why it's curious, but maybe I'm in a wrong location.
All the sidewalk that I've noticed is in the right way of this.
So we should, you've got it really wide wide where it's on the central,
so we should have plenty of room to put the utilities back in.
And then the sewer is in the middle of the street, and it's going to stay there,
we're going to do in place repair, it's kind of like we did it in the other,
the in search of form.
I'm going to be able to board this in.
After the, after the, after the, having been able more of you,
I could open a chance, other things that I kind of,
kind of what the contractor wants to do.
Any chances water linters and equities one from the hospital would I get was a 60-years-old
100 years old
I was asking the water man
He said when he's dug down he'd never found another water line in there so probably a hundred years old
Oh my gosh, that's
Amazing
This new water line last hundred years
That is the service life for for plastic pipe plastic pipe hundred years
The pipe that's in there if I got a service life about one five years
We've exceeded
We've got our men's words
So the cost for this is estimated to be
$138,000
This is the design phase
And then once we have the design phase we'll be taking two steps
Number one
This and the road project these are going to be two major projects that we're getting ready for
And all probability the water lines, sewer lines and all that would be coming from the bond issue that we proposed
And you might I'm just as reminder you might remember before the end of the year
We're going to be bringing you some options about being able to borrow money from the state
Or whether or not we would have the ability to do some type of a bond issue
So we still have to get our funding in line
We have funding for this phase of it
But once we have the phase and had the estimates
We not only have to
of glad to be there. We also have to make sure that we have the financing to do this. This could be
a probably a couple of million dollar project. This is what we're estimates. This is not a small project.
It's not even for the study that's in the budget. Correct. The money for the studies in the budget
that the money for the construction would be coming from the bond issue proceeds that we've discussed.
Questions? Other questions?
I'll show you the proof. I'll make lunch.
Now in this agenda now?
I have a question.
In the announcements?
That is the proof.
That is the time we see for the proof.